export const quizQuestions_1 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the || (OR) operator in JavaScript?',
      choices: ['Performs logical OR operation between two values', 'Performs bitwise OR operation', 'Combines two arrays', 'Concatenates two strings'],
      correctAnswer: 'Performs logical OR operation between two values',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following statements is true about the && (AND) operator in JavaScript?',
      choices: ['Returns true if both operands are true', 'Performs bitwise AND operation', 'Returns false if any operand is false', 'It is not a valid operator in JavaScript'],
      correctAnswer: 'Returns false if any operand is false',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the nullish coalescing operator (??) in JavaScript?',
      choices: ['Performs logical operation on null values', 'Returns the left-hand operand if it is null or undefined, otherwise returns the right-hand operand', 'Performs type conversion', 'Throws an error if one of the operands is null'],
      correctAnswer: 'Returns the left-hand operand if it is null or undefined, otherwise returns the right-hand operand',
    },
    {
      question: 'How does the || operator behave when encountering a truthy value?',
      choices: ['Returns the left-hand operand', 'Returns the right-hand operand', 'Throws an error', 'Skips evaluation of the right-hand operand'],
      correctAnswer: 'Returns the left-hand operand',
    },
    {
      question: 'In short-circuit evaluation using the && operator, if the left-hand operand is false, what will be the result?',
      choices: ['Returns the left-hand operand', 'Returns the right-hand operand', 'Throws an error', 'Skips evaluation of the right-hand operand'],
      correctAnswer: 'Returns the left-hand operand',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which operator is used to handle scenarios where a variable might be null or undefined and provide a default value?',
      choices: ['|| (OR) operator', '&& (AND) operator', 'Nullish coalescing operator (??)', 'Ternary operator'],
      correctAnswer: 'Nullish coalescing operator (??)',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the result of the expression: true || false?',
      choices: ['true', 'false', 'null', 'undefined'],
      correctAnswer: 'true',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the result of the expression: false && true?',
      choices: ['true', 'false', 'null', 'undefined'],
      correctAnswer: 'false',
    },
    {
      question: 'What will the nullish coalescing operator return if the left-hand operand is an empty string ("")?',
      choices: ['An empty string ("")', 'false', 'null', 'undefined'],
      correctAnswer: 'An empty string ("")',
    },
    {
      question: 'What happens when the left-hand operand of the nullish coalescing operator is a falsy value other than null or undefined?',
      choices: ['Returns the left-hand operand', 'Returns the right-hand operand', 'Throws an error', 'Skips evaluation of the right-hand operand'],
      correctAnswer: 'Returns the left-hand operand',
    },
  ],
};
